Rae Watkins Email Upon Request Address and Phone Number Upon Request

I am always eager to learn something new and love a challenge. I have 5+ years of customer service and 1+ of troubleshooting technical issues. I work well on my own as well as with a team!

Professional Experience

Dillard's, Inc., Aurora, CO

June 2022-Present

Dec. 2021-Apr. 2022

Tailor

- Fit customers to their unique measurements for the sleeve length, hem, and waist.
- Utilized geometry and measurement tools to complete requested alterations.
- Wrote bi-weekly lists of suit shipments to other stores.

Serenity Mental Health Centers, Lakewood, CO

TMS Technician

- Administered Transcranial Magnetic Stimulation Treatment.
- Maintained accurate patient medical records.
- Collaborated with Medical Professionals to determine treatment protocols.
- Acted quickly and with discretion concerning patient emergencies.
- Monitored and reported any changes in patient symptoms or behavior.
- Communicated across teams to ensure client needs were met.
- Built rapport with patients and created a safe space.

Quality DME, Inc., Lorton, VA

Apr. 2019-Aug. 2021

Patient Care Specialist

- Created CPAP reports from medical database and educated patients about their sleep data.
- Troubleshooted CPAP machine error codes on the phone and in an office setting.
- Delivered best in class customer/technical support.
- Submitted and uploaded insurance authorization documents.
- Provided exceptional support by listening to patient's needs and concerns.

Education

Southeastern University, Lakeland, FL

Bachelor of Arts in English, Business Minor, April 2016

- Graduate Cum Laude.
- Secretary/Treasurer of Sigma Tau Delta English Honor Society.

Additional Skills

Linux Fedora 36, Microsoft Office, HTML, CSS, Javascript, ReactJS, Python